С меня хватит!
Я больше не могу готовиться к тесту!
Игровые автоматы ждут.
Раз так, ничего другого не остаётся.
Эй, Нисиката, пошли с нами.
Будешь много готовиться - отупеешь.
Не, я продолжу готовиться….
Вот как!
Удачи!
Вперёд, игры ждут!
Какую из моделей выберешь?
Чёрт… Везёт.
Зато! Я должен получить хорошие оценки
на следующем тесте!
Слушай, тут свободно?
Готовишься к тестам?
А, угу…
Studying for the Test
«Подготовка к тестам»
Мимо меня только что прошли Такао-кун с друзьями.
`
Ну да. Мы вместе готовились к тестам.
Night on the Galactic Railroad
Они убежали с криками: «Вперёд, игры ждут!»
`
А ты почему не пошёл?
У меня нет времени на игры.
`
Если мои оценки будут ниже 50 баллов,
родители отберут у меня приставку.
Э… Вот оно что.
Вот блин! Зачем я ей всё рассказываю?!
Если всё ей расскажу,
она определённо не даст мне готовиться!
П-Пошутил…
О чём?
Да так, ни о чём.
В-В любом случае, не мешай…
Как грубо. Говоришь, будто я всегда встаю у тебя на пути.
В-Встаёшь ведь!
Так ведь…
Так весело дразнить тебя, Нисиката.
Может пойти куда-нибудь ещё?
Нет, тогда будет выглядеть, что Такаги-сан победила.
Такаги-сан, тебе не надо готовиться?
Угу. У меня правило. Я занимаюсь строго по два часа в день.
Вот как.
Вот это да, Такаги-сан.
Она легко входит в ТОП-10 учащихся по оценкам.
Однако… О чём она только думает?
Я уверен, Такаги-сан
имела ввиду, что обязательно мне помешает.
По-другому и быть не может.
Потому что она Такаги-сан!
Что такое?
А… Нет, ничего.
Не стоит внимания.
Я просто увидел кое-что. Не то, чтобы—
А вот тут не правильно.
Э?
В 6-ой задаче, где сказано:
«Найдите x, делённый на (-2 + 3y).»
Э? Не правильно решил?
Угу.
В чём же?
Где? Может, эмм…
Вот так.
Такаги-сан?
Мне так будет удобнее.
Так, x равен -16, а y равен -1, да?
Такаги-сан учит меня?!
Сперва, просто подставь их как-есть.
Что она задумала?!
Выпишем формулу.
А, угу…
Получится отрицательное число умноженное на
отрицательное,
поэтому следи за порядком.
А! Значит ответ будет…
Пять.
Угу, верно!
О, а вот здесь…
Такаги-сан неверноятная. Она так быстро соображает.
С-Спасибо… Я, действительно, этого не понимал.
Вот, тогда я буду учить тебя с самого начала.
T-Такаги-сан будет учить меня?
Крутяк!
Стоп! Это чертовски странно!
Чего вдруг она стала такой доброй?! Это необычно!
T-Такаги-сан, почему ты сегодня со мной так добра?
Ммм… Ты о чём?
Ну, ты так добра ко мне сегодня, поэтому…
Да… Я постоянно дразню тебя во время уроков, так что
я чувствую себя виноватой за твои низкие оценки.
Нисиката…
Прости меня за всё.
Давай постараемся для следующего теста.
Такаги-сан…
Наконец ты поменяла своё отношение!
Отлично! Я сделаю всё возможное!
Спасибо за сок.
Нет, спасибо тебе.
Сегодня я резко продвинулся в математике. Спасибо тебе.
Теперь больше шансов не лишиться приставки.
Может Такаги-сан не такой плохой человек.
Серьёзно, спасибо за сегодня, Такаги-сан.
Не стоит благодарности.
Всё таки, то, что мы разбирали
не будет на тестах.
С-Стоп! Что?
Ты же освоил подстановку?
Освоил, но всё равно!
Верни мне этот сок!
Упс, я его уже открыла.
Ты только что его открыла!
Test
«Тест»
Передаём листы с ответами вперёд.
Думаю, я справилась. По крайней мере на 90 баллов.
Отлично, просто отлично.
Юкари-тян…
Можешь объяснить это?
Я в Английском не в зуб ногой.
Э? Хочешь сказать, что в чём-то ещё разбираешься.
Я имела ввиду, худший из моих предметов!
Всё равно, как это перевест—
Прошу прощения, но мне тоже нужна проверка.
Э?! Но ты же всегда мне помогаешь с уроками!
If I get ninety percent or above
on all the tests this time,
my parents will buy any video game I want!
How do I turn this into a negative sentence?
Were you listening?!
In any case, I don't have
the time to teach you guys!
Meanie!
Which is more important?
A video game or friends?!
Yeah, yeah.
You can play video games, but
but you can't teach a video game!
Right, right.
Now that those nuisances
are gone, I should review.
All right, I'm handing out the test now.
Pass it back.
Okay, I've thoroughly reviewed
the subject before the test.
Everyone got one?
I'll score above ninety percent
on this English test as well!
First-year End of Term Test
Math
Math?!
Test Results
"Test Results."
Here.
Did you study at all?
Next, Saitou.
You look worried.
Not really…
Такаги.
Yes, sir.
You did well, as usual.
Такаги-тян, what did you get?
Can I see the answers later?
Y-You got a good score?
Yeah, but not a hundred percent.
That's Такаги-сан for you. But I should—
Next, Нисиката!
Yes, sir!
Do a little better next time, will ya?
Was it bad?
As if you're so concerned!
You're the one who taught me
stuff not covered on the test.
You say that so casually only
because you got a good score!
Hey. I said, hey.
Let's try to guess each other's score.
Whoever guesses closer wins.
You always do stuff
like this out of the blue.
I guess I don't mind.
Umm… About fifty percent?
You underestimate me too much, Такаги-сан.
I see.
Then, did you get above sixty percent?
So it's below that.
How did she know?!
Give her your poker face!
Confuse her with your poker face!
Did you get above fifty-five percent?
It is.
Why?!
So it's between fifty-five to fifty-nine.
I have to stop her from
guessing the exact score.
Okay, then…
Fifty-six.
Fifty-seven?
Fifty-eight?
Fifty-nine?
Hmm, I got it.
It's fifty-six percent.
Is that your answer, Такаги-сан?
Yep.
My test score is…
fifty-nine percent!
Sucks for you!
You were close, though.
The only thing that sucks
is your test score.
You're right, sir.
Aww, I was off by three?
You guess my score now.
If you're off within two percent, you win.
Okay! I'm gonna figure it out
based on Такаги-сан's reaction!
The teacher praised her, so
it must be above ninety percent.
Then, is it around ninety-two percent?
What was that reaction?
Is it above ninety-five?
Ninety?
Ninety-two?
She's faking it! I'm not gonna fall for it!
Такаги-сан would never make
her reaction so obvious!
Damn, she's mocking me.
I'm gonna do everything
within my power to win this!
Focus more on her expression.
Wh-What?
Oh, it's nothing. It's just that
we've been staring at each
other for a while now.
Why are you turning away?
That's a cheap shot, Такаги-сан!
I can't look at you after you said that!
Think… Just think… A hint of some sort…
To make such a fake reaction,
it must mean Такаги-сан wants me
to think she got ninety-two percent!
That also means it won't be
between ninety and ninety-four,
since they're within a two-percent difference!
Furthermore, the teacher praised
her, so it's above ninety percent.
And it's not a hundred percent, so…
it's between ninety-five and ninety-nine!
It's flawless! Perfect victory!
Такаги-сан, you scored…
ninety-seven percent!
Wrong. I got ninety-two percent.
Wh-What?!
You don't trust me enough.
I gave you a three-point handicap
on purpose for nothing.
Bookstore
"Bookstore."
100% Unrequited Love
Fierce!!
Ultimate Soccer!!
Books
No one's coming. No one's coming.
Welcome.
It'll be 420 yen, ple—
Exactly 420 yen.
Would you like a cover—
No, thank you.
Would you like a bag—
A rece—
No, thank you.
I got it!
Now, all I have to do is take
this home and read it—
Morning, Нисиката.
T-Такаги-сан? Why is she here?!
I'm taking a walk.
Did she just read my mind?!
What are you doing, Нисиката?
Crap… If she sees this…
I have to play dumb no matter what.
Well, uh… I wanted to buy a book,
but they were all out—
Wait, wait! Maybe she saw me at the register!
I-I bought volume eleven of
Fierce!! Ultimate Soccer!!
How's that?
It's popular among boys, but girls
aren't interested in that series at all.
It's a perfect answer!
I'm on a roll today—
Fierce-Soccer? Let me see. Let me see!
Huh?
Uh, but… I haven't read it yet.
Can I at least see the cover?
No, no! Definitely no!
I haven't had the chance to look at it, either.
Then, let's look at it together.
I like to look at it alone!
Aww…
I had no idea she'd be this interested.
Such a dangerous person…
I better get away from her quick.
See you later, Такаги-сан.
Um…
We coincidentally ran into each other.
Why don't we walk together for a bit?
"Coincidentally"?
You don't always run into
someone at a bookstore
this far from home so
early in the morning.
But to think there's something in
this backpack I can't let her see,
it's as though my heart's in my mouth.
I wish I were home already.
Hey, Нисиката.
Are you lying to me?
Are you lying?
Uh, um…
You didn't buy Fierce-Soccer, did you?
You bought something so
embarrassing you had to lie about it?
No… Uh…
It's just a girl's manga, right?
100% Unrequited Love?
No, I mean, that is what I got…
But how did you know?!
Well, I just happened to be passing by
when I saw you at the register,
and I saw the title as well.
She knew it all along and was playing with me.
Is it because you like the anime?
I didn't know you read that kind of stuff.
Uh, Такаги-сан!
Please don't tell anyone.
Watching it on TV is one thing,
but if people found out I'm actually
buying and reading the manga,
I'll be a laughingstock.
Hmm, should I? I mean, you did lie to me.
I've never lied to you, you know.
All right, I won't tell.
Huh?
That easily?
What?
I'm serious. Seriously, don't tell anyone.
Okay.
Seriously?! That was too easy, Такаги-сан!
You're so persistent…
Oh, then how about this?
I'll tell you my secret.
You'll be somewhat at ease
knowing my secret, too, right?
Huh? Uh, yeah…
Then, lean closer.
Uh, okay.
I like you, Нисиката.
Huh?
Huh?! Такаги-сан? Huh?!
You're bright red!
You blush so quickly, Нисиката.
Since you lied to me,
I lied to you as payback.
Oh, a lie… You startled me.
Yep, a lie.
Of course I'm lying.
I'm going this way, so see you.
Right. Bye-bye, see you.
A lie, huh?
Oh, Нисиката.
I want to read 100% Unrequited Love
too, so can I borrow it next time?
Don't say it out loud, Такаги-сан!
Shelter from the Rain
"Shelter from the Rain."
It started raining so suddenly.
I wonder if it's going to stop soon.
Hmm, I don't know…
Aww, even my socks got wet.
How about you, Нисиката?
I-I can kinda see through, Такаги-сан!
Are you listening?
Uh, yeah, right…
Keep calm! Keep calm!
If she realizes I'm panicking,
I'll be branded as a pervert!
Yeah, I hope it'll stop soon.
I wanna go home soon because there's
an anime I wanna watch past five.
It's Fierce-Soccer, by the way.
The one you bought at the bookstore?
Oh, wait. That was 100% Unrequited Love.
Y-You promised you wouldn't say anything!
But I can talk to you about it, right?
You're the person in question, after all.
I hope it stops soon.
Uhh, yeah…
Aww, it's a little wet.
Hey, Нисиката. Do you have your P.E. shirt?
Huh? Uh, yeah…
Can I borrow it? I'll wash
it and return it to you.
I want to change out of this.
Change out of it? To my P.E. shirt? Here?
Yeah. My shirt's wet. I feel gross.
But…
Besides, it seems like you're having
trouble deciding where to look.
She noticed.
Can you turn the other way?
Y-Yeah…
You managed to stay pretty dry, huh?
Yeah.
How?
Oh, you used your bag as an umbrella?
Y-Yeah…
I see. I had to hold my bike.
Right…
You can look if you want.
Uh, Такаги-сан? What are you say—
I'm done changing.
Why are you flustered?
She's toying with me!
Hey, you want to make a bet
on whether or not the rain will stop
by the time the town clock strikes five?
The loser has to do
anything the winner wants.
Okay.
What's your bet?
The rain won't stop.
Then, I'll bet the rain will stop.
If the rain stops, I can go home
and watch Fierce-Soccer.
If the rain doesn't stop,
I get to order Такаги-сан around.
I win either way!
I feel better now that I've changed my shirt.
Thanks, Нисиката.
Don't mention it.
It smells kinda sweaty, though.
It's summer. Of course it does!
The fabric that was on my body
is touching Такаги-сан's.
No! What am I thinking?!
A cat…
Oh, hey.
Are you here to take shelter?
Come here.
He's cute, but be careful.
He scratches.
You want your shirt back?
No, I'm fine.
Why don't you wear my P.E. shirt?
Huh?
It's a little wet, but it's better
than what you're wearing.
The fabric that was touching
Такаги-сан's body will be…
You done changing?
Don't look! Jeez!
I feel as if I'm doing something naughty.
It smells good.
I guess I win.
What should I make you do?
Oh, well. Fierce-Soccer will be
waiting for me when I get home.
Let's just get this over with
and run home.
Hey, Нисиката.
It stopped raining, so let's go
somewhere before we go home.
But Такаги-сан, I…
You promised the loser
would obey, right? Let's go!
Aww…